Doors open for those who push.
The After Party is a comedy, music film directed by Ian Edelman.
When an aspiring rapper goes viral for the wrong
reasons, he thinks his career is sunk.
But a wild party gives him one more chance to make it right.
Owen Ellison, played by Kyle Harvey.
Jeff Levine, played by Harrison Holzer.
Alicia Levine, played by Shelley Hennig.
Jessica, played by Jamie Choi.
Blasia, played by Teyana Taylor.
Bernard, played by Jordan Rock.
The After Party is a 2018 comedy film written and directed by Ian Edelman.
The film stars Kyle Harvey, Harrison Holzer, Shelley Hennig, Teyana Taylor, Jordan Rock, Amin
Joseph, Andy Buckley, Blair Underwood and Scott Mescudi, also featuring several cameos.
The film was released on August 24, 2018, by Netflix
to negative reviews from critics.
The tone is lighthearted.